const quiz04 = [
  {
    question: "[국외영화] ㅌㅇㅌㄴ",
    answer: "타이타닉",
  },
  {
    question: "[국외영화] ㅎㄹㅍㅌ",
    answer: "해리포터",
  },
  {
    question: "[국외영화] ㅇㅌㅅㅌㄹ",
    answer: "인터스텔라",
  },
  {
    question: "[국외영화] ㅁㅌㄹㅅ",
    answer: "매트릭스",
  },
  {
    question: "[국내영화] ㄱㅎㅈㅇ",
    answer: "극한직업",
  },
  {
    question: "[국내영화] ㅇㄷㅂㅇ",
    answer: "올드보이",
  },
  {
    question: "[국외영화] ㅎㅇㅇ ㅇㅈㅇㄴ ㅅ",
    answer: "하울의 움직이는 성",
  },
  {
    question: "[국외영화] ㅇㅅㅅ",
    answer: "인셉션",
  },
  {
    question: "[국내영화] ㄱㅅㅊ",
    answer: "기생충",
  },
  {
    question: "[국내영화] ㅈㅂㄸ",
    answer: "좀비딸",
  },
];

export default quiz04;
